University Update; Collection ua397
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
University Update Collection
1952-2006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Office of University Relations
ua397
6.2 cubic ft.
This collection consists of the University Update publication, as well as its predecessor publications produced by the same office.
Box 1
Administrative History
UAlbany has produced a number of different publications throughout its history targeted at members of the faculty. From 1952 to 2006, the Office of University Relations and its predecessors produced a series of publications aimed at keeping members of the faculty informed of campus events, university news, outside press coverage of the University, and faculty activities and publications. While these publications went by different titles over the years, the university's faculty and staff were always the primary audience. The Faculty Bulletin of Information (FBI) was a weekly general interest newsletter of campus and faculty activity published by Elmer Matthews of the Placement Office until 1964 November. After this date publication was taken over by the Public Relations Office. The FBI was succeeded by Campus Courier (1966-1969). Following the Campus Courier were the Tower Tribune, the University News, and the University Update. The University Update appears to have ceased publication in May of 2006.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of issues of the University Update (1987-2006) as well as its predecessor publications, the University News (1978-1986), the Tower Tribune (1970-1977) the Campus Courier (1966-1969) and the Faculty Bulletin of Information (1952-1966). These newsletters were produced by the University Relations Office and its predecessors.
Arrangement
Materials in each series have been arranged chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
College Publications; Newsletters; UAlbany Reference Collections
- Faculty Bulletin of Information, 1952-1966; 1
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of issues of the university publication Faculty Bulletin of Information.
- Campus Courier, 1966-1969; 2
  This series consists of issues of the university publication Campus Courier.
- Tower Tribune, 1970-1977; 3
  This series consists of issues of the university publication Tower Tribune.
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1970 February 2 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 2, 1970 February 9 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 3, 1970 February 16 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 4, 1970 February 23 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 5, 1970 March 2 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 6, 1970 March 9 (Box 3, Item 6)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 7, 1970 March 16 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 8, 1970 March 23 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 9, 1970 April 6 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 10, 1970 April 13 (Box 3, Item 10)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 11, 1970 April 20 (Box 3, Item 11)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 12, 1970 April 27 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 13, 1970 May 4 (Box 3, Item 13)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 14, 1970 May 18 (Box 3, Item 14)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 15, 1970 May 25 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - Tower Tribune, Special Research, Issue 1, 1970 May (Box 3, Item 16)
  - Tower Tribune, Special Research, Issue 2, 1970 May (Box 3, Item 17)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 16, 1970 June 29 (Box 3, Item 18)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 17, 1970 July 6 (Box 3, Item 19)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 18, 1970 July 13 (Box 3, Item 20)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 19, 1970 July 20 (Box 3, Item 21)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 20, 1970 July 27 (Box 3, Item 22)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 21, 1970 August 3 (Box 3, Item 23)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 1, No. 22, 1970 August 10 (Box 3, Item 24)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 1, 1970 August 31 (Box 3, Item 25)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 2, 1970 September 8 (Box 3, Item 26)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 3, 1970 September 14 (Box 3, Item 27)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 4, 1970 September 21 (Box 3, Item 28)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 5, 1970 September 28 (Box 3, Item 29)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 6, 1970 October 5 (Box 3, Item 30)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 7, 1970 October 12 (Box 3, Item 31)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 8, 1970 October 19 (Box 3, Item 32)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 9, 1970 October 26 (Box 3, Item 33)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 10, 1970 November 2 (Box 3, Item 34)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 11, 1970 November 9 (Box 3, Item 35)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 12, 1970 November 16 (Box 3, Item 36)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 13, 1970 November 23 (Box 3, Item 37)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 14, 1970 November 30 (Box 3, Item 38)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 15, 1970 December 7 (Box 3, Item 39)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 16, 1970 December 14 (Box 3, Item 40)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 17, 1971 January 18 (Box 3, Item 41)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 18, 1971 January 25 (Box 3, Item 42)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 19, 1971 February 1 (Box 3, Item 43)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 20, 1971 February 8 (Box 3, Item 44)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 21, 1971 February 15 (Box 3, Item 45)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 22, 1971 February 22 (Box 3, Item 46)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 23, 1971 March 1 (Box 3, Item 47)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 24, 1971 March 8 (Box 3, Item 48)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 25, 1971 March 15 (Box 3, Item 49)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 26, 1971 March 22 (Box 3, Item 50)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 27, 1971 March 29 (Box 3, Item 51)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 28, 1971 April 12 (Box 3, Item 52)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 29, 1971 April 19 (Box 3, Item 53)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 30, 1971 April 26 (Box 3, Item 54)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 31, 1971 May 3 (Box 3, Item 55)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 32, 1971 June 28 (Box 3, Item 56)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 33, 1971 July 6 (Box 3, Item 57)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 34, 1971 July 12 (Box 3, Item 58)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 35, 1971 July 19 (Box 3, Item 59)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 36, 1971 July 26 (Box 3, Item 60)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 37, 1971 August 2 (Box 3, Item 61)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 2, No. 38, 1971 August 9 (Box 3, Item 62)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 1, 1971 August 30 (Box 3, Item 63)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 2, 1971 September 7 (Box 3, Item 64)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 3, 1971 September 13 (Box 3, Item 65)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 4, 1971 September 20 (Box 3, Item 66)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 5, 1971 September 27 (Box 3, Item 67)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 6, 1971 October 4 (Box 3, Item 68)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 7, 1971 October 11 (Box 3, Item 69)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 8, 1971 October 18 (Box 3, Item 70)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 9, 1971 October 25 (Box 3, Item 71)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 10, 1971 November 1 (Box 3, Item 72)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 11, 1971 November 8 (Box 3, Item 73)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 12, 1971 November 15 (Box 3, Item 74)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 13, 1971 November 22 (Box 3, Item 75)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 14, 1971 November 30 (Box 3, Item 76)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 15, 1971 December 6 (Box 3, Item 77)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 16, 1971 December 13 (Box 3, Item 78)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 17, 1972 January 18 (Box 3, Item 79)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 18, 1972 January 24 (Box 3, Item 80)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 19, 1972 January 31 (Box 3, Item 81)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 20, 1972 February 7 (Box 3, Item 82)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 21, 1972 February 14 (Box 3, Item 83)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 22, 1972 February 21 (Box 3, Item 84)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 23, 1972 February 28 (Box 3, Item 85)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 24, 1972 March 6 (Box 3, Item 86)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 25, 1972 March 13 (Box 3, Item 87)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 26, 1972 March 20 (Box 3, Item 88)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 27, 1972 March 27 (Box 3, Item 89)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 28, 1972 April 10 (Box 3, Item 90)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 29, 1972 April 17 (Box 3, Item 91)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 30, 1972 April 24 (Box 3, Item 92)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 31, 1972 May 1 (Box 3, Item 93)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 32, 1972 May 8 (Box 3, Item 94)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 33, 1972 June 26 (Box 3, Item 95)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 34, 1972 July 3 (Box 3, Item 96)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 35, 1972 July 10 (Box 3, Item 97)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 36, 1972 July 17 (Box 3, Item 98)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 37, 1972 July 24 (Box 3, Item 99)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 38, 1972 July 31 (Box 3, Item 100)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 3, No. 38, 1972 August 28 (Box 3, Item 101)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 1, 1972 August 28 (Box 3, Item 102)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 2, 1972 September 5 (Box 3, Item 103)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 3, 1972 September 11 (Box 3, Item 104)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 4, 1972 September 18 (Box 3, Item 105)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 5, 1972 September 25 (Box 3, Item 106)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 6, 1972 October 2 (Box 3, Item 107)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 7, 1972 October 9 (Box 3, Item 108)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 8, 1972 October 16 (Box 3, Item 109)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 9, 1972 October 23 (Box 3, Item 110)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 10, 1972 October 30 (Box 3, Item 111)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 11, 1972 November 6 (Box 3, Item 112)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 12, 1972 November 13 (Box 3, Item 113)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 13, 1972 November 20 (Box 3, Item 114)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 14, 1972 November 27 (Box 3, Item 115)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 15, 1972 December 4 (Box 3, Item 116)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 16, 1972 December 11 (Box 3, Item 117)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 17, 1973 January 15 (Box 3, Item 118)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 18, 1973 January 22 (Box 3, Item 119)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 19, 1973 January 29 (Box 3, Item 120)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 20, 1973 February 5 (Box 3, Item 121)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 21, 1973 February 12 (Box 3, Item 122)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 22, 1973 February 19 (Box 3, Item 123)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 23, 1973 February 26 (Box 3, Item 124)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 24, 1973 March 6 (Box 3, Item 125)
  - Tower Tribune, Vol. 4, No. 25, 1973 March 19 (Box 3, Item 126)
- University News, 1978-1986; 4
  This series consists of issues of the university publication University News.
- University Update, 1987-2006; 5
  This series consists of copies of the university publication University Update.
- University Update Online Editions, 1997 September 3 - 2003 June 2; 6
  This series consists of digital versions of the university publication University Update preserved via a webcrawler. Files in this series generally convey the same information as the materials in the previous series, although it appears that some online issues of the Update included additional articles.
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 1, 1997 September 3
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 2, 1997 September 17
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 3, 1997 October 1
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 4, 1997 October 15
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 5, 1997 October 29
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 6, 1997 November 12
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 7, 1997 December 3
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 8, 1998 January 28
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 9, 1998 February 11
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 10, 1998 February 25
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 11, 1998 March 11
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 12, 1998 March 25
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 13, 1998 April 8
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 14, 1998 April 22
  - University Update Volume 21 Number 15, 1998 May 6
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 1, 1998 September 2
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 2, 1998 September 16
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 3, 1998 September 30
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 4, 1998 October 14
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 5, 1998 October 28
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 6, 1998 November 11
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 7, 1998 December 2
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 8, 1999 January 27
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 9, 1999 February 10
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 10, 1999 February 24
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 11, 1999 March 10
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 12, 1999 March 24
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 13, 1999 April 7
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 14, 1999 April 21
  - University Update Volume 22 Number 15, 1999 May 5
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 1, 1999 September 8
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 2, 1999 September 22
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 3, 1999 October 6
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 4, 1999 October 21
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 5, 1999 November 3
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 6, 1999 November 17
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 7, 1999 December 2
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 8, 2000 January 19
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 9, 2000 February 2
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 10, 2000 February 17
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 11, 2000 March 1
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 12, 2000 March 15
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 13, 2000 March 29
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 14, 2000 April 13
  - University Update Volume 23 Number 15, 2000 May 3
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 1, 2000 September 7
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 2, 2000 September 21
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 3, 2000 October 5
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 4, 2000 October 19
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 5, 2000 November 2
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 6, 2000 November 16
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 7, 2000 November 30
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 8, 2000 December 14
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 9, 2001 January 25
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 10, 2001 February 13
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 11, 2001 February 22
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 12, 2001 March 9
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 13, 2001 March 22
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 14, 2001 April 5
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 15, 2001 April 19
  - University Update Volume 24 Number 16, 2001 May 3
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 1, 2001 August 30
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 2, 2001 September 13
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 3, 2001 September 27
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 4, 2001 October 12
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 5, 2001 October 25
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 6, 2001 November 8
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 7, 2001 November 30
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 8, 2001 December 13
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 9, 2002 January 31
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 10, 2002 February 14
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 11, 2002 February 28
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 12, 2002 March 14
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 13, 2002 March 28
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 14, 2002 April 11
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 15, 2002 April 25
  - University Update Volume 25 Number 16, 2002 May 9
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 1, 2002 September 12
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 2, 2002 October 10
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 3, 2002 November 7
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 4, 2002 December 12
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 5, 2003 January 31
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 6, 2003 February 27
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 7, 2003 March 27
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 8, 2003 May 8
  - University Update Volume 26 Number 9, 2003 June 2